Guide to the Russell Van Nest Black papers, 1919-1968.
Black, Russell Van Nest papers
- Series I. Correspondence
  - 1946-1948
    - Correspondence with Leslie O'Gwynn, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      Salary, Vacation, Etc.
    - P General, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      Ewing, New Jersey. Planning Practice. Institute of Local and State Government.
    - P Prospects, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      Parsippany-Troy Hills, New Jersey; Princeton, New Jersey. Zoning and Planning.
    - Pennsylvania State Planning Board, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      Francis A. Pitkin.
    - Pennsylvania Planning Board, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Personal Matters, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Planning and Zoning Program for the Borough of Mendham, New Jersey, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      George Wallace; G. J. Panille. Mendham Township Planning Board.
    - Princeton, New Jersey, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      Warner Wood.
    - R General, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 21)
      Robert Randall.
    - R Prospects, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      Roseland, New Jersey. Borough of Roseland.
    - Readington Township, New Jersey, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      County Planning. John W. Field.
    - Readington Township, New Jersey, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - S General, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - S Prospects, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 26)
      Lawrence, Pennsylvania; Statesville, North Carolina. Zoning. Statesville Chamber of Commerce.
    - School Board, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 27)
      School Planning - Frederick E. Tanger. Public Schools of Bucks County.
    - School Board, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 28)
      Solebury Township School Board. New Hope Solebury Joint Public Schools.
    - South Orange, New Jersey, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      Robert Upjohn Redpath, Jr; James O'Hearn. Planning and Development Board of the Village of South Orange.
    - South Orange, New Jersey, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 30)
      Zoning. Robert U. Redpath, Jr. Planning and Development Board of the Village of South Orange.
    - T, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 31)
      Trenton, New Jersey. References. Armand Tibbitts; A. D. Taylor.
    - T General, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - T Prospects, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 33)
      Hopewell, New Jersey. Zoning.
    - Trenton, New Jersey, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 34)
      Trenton Planning Board.
    - Trexler Estate, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 35)
      Allentown, Pennsylvania. Estate of Harry Trexler.
    - U, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - U General, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - V, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - W, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 40)
      Multiple Housing.
    - W General, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 41)
      Borough of Watchung.
    - W Prospects, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 42)
      Wall Township, Pennsylvania. Zoning and Planning.
    - Wayne Township, New Jersey, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Wayne Township, New Jersey, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Winston-Salem, North Carolina, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 45-47)
      Leslie O'Gwynn; William Hoyt.
    - Winston-Salem, North Carolina, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 48, 49)
      Zoning and Planning; William Hoyt; Leslie O'Gwynn
    - Winston-Salem, North Carolina (Special), 1948 (Box 16, Folder 50)
      Zoning and Planning. Armand Tibbitts.
    - Y Prospects, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 51)
      Bucks County, Pennsylvania.
  - 1948-1953
    - A-file, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - A-file, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 53)
      re: Article on Winston-Salem. American City.
    - A General, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 54)
      Post-war Planning - Norris, Tennessee; Alburquerque, New Mexico. Tracy Augur.
    - Aero Service Corporation, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - American City Planning Institute, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 57)
      City Planning Society. Minutes.
    - American Institute of Planners, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 58)
      Planning Society. Charles Blessing, "Surveying and Maping for Modern City Planning", N.Y. ASCE, 1950. Planning Education. Constitution.
    - American Institute of Planners, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 59)
      Fred Adams.
    - American Planning and Civic Association, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 60)
      Routine Personal Correspondence. Harlean James.
    - American Planning and Civic Association, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - American Society of Civil Engineers, undated (Box 16, Folder 62)
      Charles Blessing.
    - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 66)
      Zoning; digest. Housing Legislation (Act of 1949)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 67)
      Planning Practice. Walter Blucher.
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - Applications, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Applications, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Applications, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - B-file, 1943, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 72)
      Urban Redevelopment Legislation, Thomas Bill. Alfred Bettman.
    - B-file, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 73)
      Bernards, New Jersey. Zoning. Personal Correspondence.
    - B General, 1948-1949 (Box 16, Folder 74)
      Watchung. American Institute of Planners. Zoning. Fred Bigger. Bryant's Nursersies.
    - Bernards Township, New Jersey, 1948-1949 (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - Bernards Township, New Jersey, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - Bucks County Farm, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - Bucks County Farm, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 78)
    - Bucks County Farm, 1949, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 79)
    - C-file, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 80)
      Chambersburg, Pennsylvania; Chatham, Pennsylvania; Clifton, Pennsylvania. Zoning. Planning and Zoning Commission of Chambersburg.
    - C-file, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 81)
      Cleona, Pennsylvania; Nashville Tennessee; Mount Pocono, Pennsylvania; West Palm Beach, Florida. Zoning. Housing. Cleona Borough Zoning and Planning Commission; Clarke, Rapvano and Holleran.
    - C General, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 82)
      Solebury, Pennsylvania. Zoning. Arthur Comey. Columbia University.
    - Christmas Trees, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 83)
    - Christmas Trees, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 84)
    - Christmas Trees, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 85)
    - Clifton, New Jersey, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 86)
    - Clifton, New Jersey, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Cornell University, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - D-file, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Delaware County, Pennsylvania. Delaware County Planning Commission.
    - D-file, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - D General, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Includes Personal Correspondence. Earle Draper.
    - E-file, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      East Windsor, New Jersey. Zoning
    - E-file, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - E General, 1949-1950 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      George School.
    - F-file, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - F General, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - G-file, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - G-file, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      Glen Rock, New Jersey. Zoning.
    - G General, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - H-file, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      Includes Personal Correspondence. B. Antrim Haldeman.
    - H-file, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      Hightstown, New Jersey. Zoning.
    - H General, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      Highway Planning - Massachusetts; Highland Park, New Jersey. Zoning. B. Antrim Haldeman. Borough of Hiland Park; Commonwealth of Massachusetts.
    - I-file, 1948, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      Institute of Local and State Government; University of Pennsylvania.
    - J-file, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      Jackson, Mississippi.
    - J-file, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - J General, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - K-file, 1950-1951 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      Bucks County, Pennsylvania. State Legislation.
    - K General, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - L-file, 1949-1950 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - L-file, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      Lewistown, Pennsylvania. Land Development.
    - L General, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      League of Women Voters.
    - Lower Paxton Township, Pennsylvania, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Lower Paxton Township, Pennsylvania, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Lower Paxton Township, Pennsylvania, 1950-1951 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      Zoning. Board of Supervisors.
    - M-file, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      Recreational Planning - Mount Vernon, Ohio. Re: "Lionshead Lake vs. Township of Wayne". B. Williams.
    - M-file, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 30)
      Mount Vernon, Ohio; Georgia Institute of Technology. Re: "Lions vs Township of Wayne". Russell Montney. Markley & Broadhurst.
    - M General, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 31)
      Mount Joy, Pennsylvania; Mount Vernon, Ohio. Zoning. Clarence Schock.
    - Mercer County New Jersey - Plan, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Mercer County, New Jersey, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Morrisville, Pennsylvania, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - N-file, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 35)
      New Brunswick, New Jersey. Housing. New Brunswick Housing Authority.
    - N General, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 36)
      Niagara Falls, New York; Newark, New Jersey; York, Pennsylvania. Zoning.
    - New Jersey State Planning Board, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - New Jersey State Planning Board, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - New Jersey State Planning, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Nutley, New Jersey, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Nutley, New Jersey, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Nutley, New Jersey, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - O-file, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 43)
      Includes Personal Correspondence. Leslie O'Gwynn.
    - O-file, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 44)
      Cleveland, Ohio; Delaware, Ohio. Leslie O'Gwynn.
    - O General, 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 45)
      Charlotte, North Carolina; Iowa State; Winston-Salem, North Carolina. Planning Education. Leslie O'Gwynn.
    - Office (Insurance, etc.), 1949 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Office (Insurance, etc.), 1950 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Office (Insurance, etc.), 1951 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - P-file, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - P-file, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 50)
      Planning Practice. Hugh Pomeroy.
    - P General, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 51)
      Clifton, New Jersey. Planning Services. Passaic-Bergen Community Planning Association.
    - Pennsylvania Planning Board, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Pennsylvania State Planning Board, 1949-1950 (Box 17, Folder 53)
      Morrisville, Pennsylvania; New Jersey. Housing. Carnegie - Illinois Steel Corporation; Commonwealth of Pennsylvania Department of Commerce.
    - Pennsylvania State Planning Board, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - R-file, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 55)
      Allentown, Pennsylvania. Zoning.
    - R-file, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 56)
      Ridgway, Pennsylvania. Planning Practice. Zoning. Clifton Rogers. Ridgway Borough Zoning Commission.
    - R General, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 57)
      Routine Personal Correspondence. Bob Randall.
    - S-file, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 58)
      Allentown. Zoning
    - S-file, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 59)
      Solebury, Pennsylvania. Zoning. Personal Correspondence. Edgar Smith.
    - S General, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 60)
      Sea Isle City, New Jersey; Solebury, Pennsylvania. Zoning. Land Development. Ladislas Segoe.
    - Solebury Cooperative, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - South Orange, New Jersey, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - T-file, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 63)
      Allentown, Pennsylvania; Trenton, New Jersey. Housing Authority of City of Trenton.
    - T General, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 64)
      Allentown, Pennsylvania. Land Development. Armand Tibbitts.
    - Trenton, Lawrence & Ewring Townships, New Jersey, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Trenton, Lawrence & Ewring Townships, New Jersey, 1948, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 66)
      Planning and Zoning. Trenton Planning Board. Report
    - Trenton Metropolitan Area, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Trenton Redevelopment Authority, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 68)
      Housing.
    - U-file, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 69)
      Morrisville, Pennsylvania. United States Steel Corporation
    - U General, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - V-file, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - W-file, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 72)
      Wayne, New Jersey; West Orange, New Jersey. Zoning. Re: "Lionshead Lake vs. Wayne Township".
    - W-file, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 73)
      Wayne, New Jersey. Zoning re: "Lion Lake vs. Township of Wayne".
    - W General, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 74)
      Wayne, New Jersey. Zoning. Township of Wayne.
    - Winston-Salem, North Carolina, 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 75)
    - Winston-Salem, North Carolina, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 76)
    - Winston-Salem, North Carolina, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 77)
    - XYZ-file, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 78)
      Yardley, Pennsylvania. Yardley Borough Planning Commission.
  - 1952-1956
    - A-file, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 79)
      Zoning. Charles Agle.
    - A-file, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 80)
      Abington, Pennsylvania. Planning Education. Planning Profession. Frederick Adams. Montgomery; McCraken; Walker; Rhoads.
    - A-file, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 81)
      Allentown, Pennsylvania. American Planning and Civic Association
    - A-file, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 82)
      American Planning and Civic Association.
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 83)
    - American City Planning Institute, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 84)
    - American Institute of Planners, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 85)
    - American Institute of Planners, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 86)
      Includes Memorandum.
    - American Society of Civil Engineers, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 87)
    - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 88)
    - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 89)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 90)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 91)
      Zoning Digest
    - Applications, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 92)
    - B-file, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 93)
      Bucks County, Pennsylvania; Cleveland, Ohio. Land Development. Mrs. William Mather.
    - B-file, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 94)
      Bucks County, Pennsylvania; Bridgewater, Pennsylvania; Bound Brook, New Jersey. Zoning. Bucks County Planning Commission; Township of Bridgewater.
    - B-file, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 95)
      Regional Planning - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Planning Practice. Zoning.
    - Bucks County, Pennsylvania, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 96)
      Bucks County Planning Commission.
    - Bucks County, Pennsylvania, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 97)
    - Bucks County Farm, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 98)
    - Bucks County Farm, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 99)
      Personal Business. Ross & Smith.
    - C-file, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 100)
      Borough of Cleona, Pennsylvania; Clifton, New Jersey. City of Clifton; Department of Commerce.
    - C-file, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 101)
      Trenton, New Jersey; Cornell; Clifton, New Jersey; Clark, New Jersey. Zoning. Arthur Comey. Conrell University - College of Architecture; Citizens Advisory Comimittee to Planning Board; Township of Clark, New Jersey.
    - C-file, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 102)
      Camden, New Jersey; Cape May, New Jersey. Zoning.
    - Christmas Trees, 1952-1953 (Box 17, Folder 103-104)
      Business Correspondence. (Christmas tree business.)
    - D-file, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - D-file, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      Delaware Valley Protective Association.
    - Doylestown, Pennsylvania., 1952 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      Zoning and Planning. Borough Planning Commission.
    - Doylestown, Pennsylvania., 1953 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      Zoning and Planning. Doylestown Borough Council.
    - Doylestown, Pennsylvania., 1954 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      J. Carroll Molloy. Doylestown Borough Council.
    - E-file, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      Trenton, New Jersey; Elizabeth, New Jersey. Zoning. Engineering News - Record.
    - E-file, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      Elizabeth, New Jersey; East Windsor, New Jersey. Planning and Zoning. East Windsor Township; Elizabeth Planning Board.
    - E-file, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      Edgewater, New Jersey; Ewing, New Jersey. Zoning. George Bohlinger. Edgewater Park Township Planning Board.
    - Edgewater, New Jersey, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      Planning and Zoning. Planning Board, Borough of Edgewater
    - Edgewater, New Jersey, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - F-file, 1951-1952 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      Morrisville, Pennsylvania; Falls Township, Pennsylvania; Fairfax, Virginia.
    - F-file, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      Highway Planning - Pennsylvania. Pennsylvania Roadside Council.
    - F-file, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      Flemington, New Jersey; Middlesex, New Jersey; Franklin, Pennsylvania. Zoning
    - G-file, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - G-file, 1952-1953 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - G-file, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      Gettysburg, Pennsylvania.
    - H-file, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      Hamilton Township, New Jersey; Hanover County, Pennsylvania. Zoning.
    - H-file, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      Includes Personal Correspondence; Zoning. Donald Hedges.
    - H-file, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      Hillsborough, New Jersey.
    - Hamilton Township, New Jersey, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 20)
      Hamilton Township Planning Board.
    - Hamilton Township, New Jersey, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - I-file, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 22)
      Bayonne, New Jersey. Planning Practice. State of New Jersey-0 Department of Law and Public Safety.
    - J-file, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - J-file, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - K-file, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - K-file, 1952-1953 (Box 18, Folder 26)
      Personal Business
    - K-file, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - L-file, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 28)
      Lawrence Township, New Jersey; Trenton, New Jersey; Yardley, Pennsylvania; Lewistown, Pennsylvania. Zoning and Planning. Dorothy Bayless. New Jersey Department of Conservation and Economic Development; Borough of Lewistown.
    - L-file, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 29)
      Lawrenceville, New Jersey; Borough of Little Silver, New Jersey. Zoning. Lawrence Township Planning Board.
    - L-file, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 30)
      Lancaster, Pennsylvania; Long Branch, New Jersey; Lansing, Michigan. Planning Board of Long Branch; City of Lancaster.
    - Lawrence Township, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 31)
      Lawrence, New Jersey. Lawrence Township Planning Board.
    - Lower Makefield Township, Pennsylvania, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 32)
      Planning and Zoning. Commonwealth of Pennsylvania.
    - Lower Makefield Township, Pennsylvania, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - M-file, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 34)
      Paterson, New Jersey; Bucks County. Land Development.
    - M-file, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 35)
      Patterson, New Jersey; Hillsborough, New Jersey. Saul Mann.
    - M-file, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 36)
      Wayne, New Jersey; Morrisville, Pennsylvania. Zoning. Federal Grants in mid-local planning. Russell Montney. Borough of Morrisville.
    - Mercer County, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Morrisville, Pennsylvania, 1951-1952 (Box 18, Folder 38)
      Planning and Zoning. Borough Planning Commission.
    - Morrisville, Pennsylvania, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 39)
      Borough of Morrisville, Pennsylvania. Borough Planning Commission.
    - Morrisville, Pennsylvania, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - N-file, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 41)
      Niagara Falls, New York; New Brunswick, New Jersey. Niagara Falls Chamber of Commerce.
    - N-file, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - N-file, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 43)
      Bucks County, Pennsylvania; New Jersey.
    - New Jersey State, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 44)
      Planning Legislation; Land Subdivision. Fred Stickel. State of New Jersey Department of Conservation and Economic Development.
    - New Jersey State, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 45)
      State of New Jersey Department of Conservation and Economic Development.
    - New Jersey State Planning Board, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Nutley, New Jersey, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Nutley, New Jersey, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Nutley, New Jersey, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - O-file, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 50)
      Cleveland, Ohio. Leslie O'Gwynn
    - O-file, undated (Box 18, Folder 51)
      Oil City, Pennsylvania. Joseph Barr, Jr.
    - P-file, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 52)
      University of Pennsylvania. Planning Education. F. A. Pitkin. Peddie School.
    - P-file, 1952-1953 (Box 18, Folder 53)
      Morrisville, New Jersey. Zoning. Dorothy Whiteman.
    - P-file, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Pennsylvania State, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 55)
      Bucks, Pennsylvania. Planning and Zoning.
    - Pennsylvania State, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 56)
      Commonwealth of Pennsylvania; Department of Commerce.
    - Pennsylvania State Planning Board, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - R-file, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 58)
      Riverdale, New York. Zoning. Bob Randall. Township of Riverdale.
    - R-file, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 59)
      Reading, Pennsylvania. Zoning and Planning. City Planning Commission.
    - R-file, 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 60)
      Regional Planning - Reading Pennsylvania; Millstone Valley, Pennsylvania. City Planning Commission of Reading.
    - S-file, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 61)
      Solebury, Pennsylvania; Sommerville, New Jersey; New Jersey; South Carolina. Zoning. Flavel Shurtleff. Borough of Somerville.
    - S-file, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 62)
      Shrewsbury, New Jersey. Zoning. Katherine Salzer. Planning Board Borough of Shrewsbury, New Jersey.
    - S-file, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 63)
      State Planning - Trenton, New Jersey; Solebury, Pennsylvania; South Carolina. Zoning.
    - T-file, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - T-file, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - T-file, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 66)
      Haddon Field, New Jersey; Allentown, Pennsylvania. Land Development. 20th Century Construction Co., Inc.; Estate of Harry C. Trexler.
    - Trenton, New Jersey, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 67)
      Zoning. Trenton Planning Board.
    - Trenton, New Jersey, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Trenton City, 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Trenton Redevelopment, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 70)
      Housing Authority of City of Trenton.
    - Trenton Redevelopment, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 71)
      Urban Redevelopment. Housing Authority of City of Trenton.
    - Trenton Redevelopment, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 72)
      Housing Redevelopment. J. Conner French.
    - U-file, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 73)
      Southampton, Pennsylvania. Zoning; Urban Taxation. Jane Unwin. Upper Southampton Township.
    - U-file, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 74)
      Jupiter, Florida. Land Development. Upholsterers' International Union.
    - U-file, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 75)
      Palm Beach, Florida. Housing Development. Rufus Nims.
    - V-file, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - V-file, 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 77)
      Palm Springs, Florida. Housing Development. Urban Land Institute.
    - V-file, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - W-file, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 79)
      West Windsor, New Jersey.
    - W-file, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 80)
      Waldwick, New Jersey; District of Columbia. Zoning. Government of the District of Columbia.
    - W-file, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 81)
      Wheeling, West Virginia; Wayne, New Jersey. Zoning.
    - W-file, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 82)
      Road Planning - Wynnewood, Pennsylvania; Willamsport, Pennsylvania. Wynnewood Civic Association; Greater Williamsport Chamber of Commerce.
    - Winston-Salem, North Carolina, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 83)
      W. K. Hoyt. City Planning Board.
    - Winston-Salem, North Carolina, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - Y-file, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 85)
      Bucks, Pennsylvania; Yardsley, Pennsylvania. Zoning.
    - XYZ-file, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 86)
      Yardsley, Pennsylvania. Henry A. Ludeke
  - 1955-1957
    - A-file, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - A-file, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 88)